(Prof Crawley(arriving):)Why be polite to the world's leading
expert on the dung beetle?
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
are you Professor Crawley?
(Prof Crawley:)Who wants to know?
(Sheldon:)I'm Dr. Cooper,
from the Physics Department.
(Prof Crawley:)-Couldn't wait, huh?
-I'm sorry?
(Prof Crawley:)I haven't even packed yet
and you're already measuring my lab...
(Prof Crawley:)...for one
of your godless laser machines.
(Howard:)No, you don't understand.
We just wanna ask you a question.
(Prof Crawley:)Let me ask you one first.
What's a world-renowned entomologist
with a doctorate...
(Prof Crawley:)...and 20 years of experience,
to do with his life...
(Prof Crawley:)...when the university cuts off
the funding for his lab, huh?
(Raj:)Ask rhetorical questions
that make people uncomfortable?
[CHUCKLES]
(Prof Crawley:)What's your deal?
(Prof Crawley:)Are they planning to outsource my job
to Bangalore?
(Raj:)I'm from New Delhi.
-We should find another entomologist.
-We're here. Let's settle this.